OPUS PICTURES presents
A GOLDENTIDE PICTURES production
We were ambushed from the rear!
Who was the attacker? Was it the North?
Cannot confirm, cannot confirm!
Pull back to sector 31!
Send in reinforcement, we could all die!
Get out of there!
DMZ, 1km from the South
LEE JI-AH
KIM MIN-JUN
- Leave me.
- Sir?
Just get out of here, asshole!
Run for the GP gate! Now!
Sgt. Lee…
MUSUDAN
Salute!
Lt. Lee is reassigned to a desk job
after suffering a wrist injury.
There's also Lt. Shin Yoo-hwa,
who scored highest marks
in biochemical warfare,
and microbiology in Germany.
Written and directed by GU MO
Salute!
Sorry for bringing you
in during your training.
Sit.
Begin right away, major.
Yes, sir.
6 am on the 14th, a
search party was ambushed.
It took place in Sector 603
1km from Southern Limit Line.
Autopsy photos, it is presumed that…
Who do you think it did?
I can't… tell for sure yet.
With talk of a potential summit,
a clash in the DMZ will be a headache.
I want you to lead a
special detail to find out.
We've already selected your team.
Lt. Shin is the deputy?
That feels good.
Lt. Shin.
You're the best.
That was great work.
Really? You drank all that?
Go wash it.
I don't disrespect Lt. Shin,
but an experienced NCO
should take the role, sir.
You two went through tactical training,
and Mt. Gari infil mission.
This is not even main
mission, what's with you?
But if we're entering DMZ, we should…
What.
Is there a problem?
No, sir.
It's not fair that I got sidelined
because of this damn cast.
- When do you remove it?
- Whenever I want.
That's enough camo paint on your lips.
No bachelors in sight.
It looks like you got blood on it.
Near Civilian Control Line,
dozens of dead chickens were discovered.
According to the locals,
as high as 20 are discovered
on any given day.
Defense Ministry has yet
to release a statement…
Looks like chicken's
on our menu for a week.
Shift change.
Lt. Shin, I'm off.
Oops, this is yours. Sorry.
Later, Lee Hyun-suk.
It's Sgt. Yoo.
- Come in.
- Yes, sir
Salu…
What?
I thought I was in the wrong room.
How's your skin trouble?
I was feeling sweet tooth, thanks for this.
What's this?
Make-up of course.
Isn't that for chicks?
Lt. Shin.
Yes, sir.
Something going on?
Salute!
It's the list of members for the detail.
Briefing at HQ, 5 pm.
Are you injured?
Sir?
Sir.
Sgt. Han, did something happen in S603?
Who knows, let's head inside.
How was the field training?
No more shop talk.
Hey, Sgt. Han!
- Salute!
- Sure.
Sgt. Yoo, what brings you here?
Special detail.
Cpt. Jo's?
You too?
Am I bringing down class?
I'm used to it, Sgt. Han.
- Who's the deputy?
- Don't know.
I heard Master Sgt. Park is also selected.
The Grim Reaper?
So he's the deputy…
Let's find out.
Then I'm the junior?
Yup.
- Hey, kiddo.
- Pvt. Lee Jong-hui!
Have you seen a boar?
One stared through me during a drill,
- but my swift kick…
- I've been looking all over.
You must report to HQ for S603 detail ASAP.
Private, do your best, you'll be fine.
What are you talking about?
It's you, petty officer.
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm not falling for that again.
I did my duty.
Take care!
That chump…
Kiddo, I'll read this order form for you.
Mission Order Name: PO Roh Il-kwon
We've just crossed S883.
Let's introduce ourselves.
I'm Lt. Shin Yoo-hwa,
deputy chief of this detail.
Sgt. Han Seung-ho
from sector 3 infil squad.
Good to see you.
I'm in Sgt. Yoo's year, please be at ease.
I serve with Lt. Shin,
Sgt. Yoo of sniper squad.
Staff Sgt. Gu Yoon-gil from sector 3.
I heard you were 1st in
ATT drill, am I correct?
Yes, ma'am.
And you?
- Salute!
Salute!
Shin Yoo-hwa…
- Colonel.
- Come in.
We have no idea what happened in 603,
or why the entire search party was killed.
We must uncover the truth
and eliminate the threat.
We deploy at 0600,
when GP 426's shift ends,
until next patrol unit reports at 0600.
Exactly 24 hours.
If we're entering DMZ,
what's our rules of engagement?
We must avoid skirmish,
so ROE is limited at best.
And as such, minimize your gear.
- Check the gear.
- Yes, sir!
Salute!
This is a covert op,
so light-weight loadout,
and silencers are mandatory.
- Sgt. Yoo.
- Yes, ma'am.
Add M18 smoke grenade to the list.
The smoke grenade?
Prepare it.
Any other required gear, ma'am?
- That is all.
- Yes, ma'am.
For this detail,
remove all insignias and unit badges.
Assemble at staging area,
0500 tomorrow, dismissed.
Yes, sweetie.
A gun?!
Salute!
Sweetie, girls should have ballet…
Okay, I'll head home early,
so have dinner with granny.
Salute!
Sir, please head out early.
I'll prep the loadout fit for the mission.
- Sergeant.
- Yes, sir.
Where can I buy realistic replica guns?
Sir?
No, I don't…
She wants a gun…
My daughter…
I'm off, prep properly.
- Yes sir!
- Salute!
Salute!
I did not expect that from him.
Kiddo.
How long till your discharge?
20 days, sir.
Only 20 days left, but you volunteered?
Sir?
- We got a hero.
- That's not it.
I was the chief's radioman during training,
I guess I was assigned because of it.
Assigned, eh?
How old are you?
25, sir.
That means…
he's older than you.
Stay frosty.
- Let's go.
- Okay, I'm off.
Kiddo, no mistakes.
Salute!
They've been briefed.
I will not disappoint you for selecting me…
I did not select you.
You weren't my choice.
You're not fit for this detail.
No prior DMZ experience.
Shin, it's not too late to bail.
I'll see you at the staging area!
Salute!
Cpt. Jo was an elite since he was a cadet,
so I understand fully
why he was picked to lead.
But why overlook Sgt. Park
and assign you as his deputy?
Hey!
You called me out to tell me that?
Lieutenant, this is live combat.
Frankly, what can a woman do in there?
You can't do much, and it's bug haven.
I washed this today.
Your birthday's in 2
days, I got you a present…
That sass of hers…
Lt. Shin!
Come with me!
0508 hours
Is everything here?
Yes, Sgt. Yoo.
You have exactly 24 hours
to complete this mission.
Yes, sir!
Roll out.
Passing through S532.
Requesting mobile eye check.
Poor signal, ending transmission, over.
Here, chew.
I don't chew gum before breakfast, sir.
We all had breakfast.
Who told you to skip?
Become one with the unit.
Deputy chief.
This won't cause skin
trouble, it's top class.
30 minutes out.
So you're asking me to
check the radio signal…
Salute!
Between war room and
admin HQ, but why should I?!
I'm sorry, sir. At once!
Why am I doing petty chores?
Major's gonna bitch at me.
Cameras are attached to their boonie hats.
What the hell?
Salute!
This is a restricted room,
get the hell out, asshole!
Sorry, sir…
I'm sorry for that, colonel.
Central Forward Area
GP 325 Gate, 0600 hours
24 hours to complete this mission and evac.
- Lock and load.
2-1, 2-1.
Eagles deploying for S603, over.
GP, seal the gate and don't let anyone in.
3 members of covert ops
disguised as search party
are confirmed dead
and rest are still missing.
This op may need to be
covered up on my end.
That's right, commander.
Lt. Choi, it's the Milltary
Demarcation Line.
Cross.
- It's quite eerie here.
- Right?
Is there anything you want for your b-day?
So that's the good news.
How about a decent man, deputy?
No more small talks.
Yes, ma'am.
3-2-2, on recon route.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Deputy.
I'll go ahead.
2-1, 2-1, signal check,
requesting signal check, over.
3-2-2, 3-2-2, signal
optimal, visual sitrep?
Eagles flying blind, over.
There was no restricted sign.
Or at least send me a memo.
The radio's on, but what am I to do?
RESTRICTED AREA
Analyzing its clot state,
it's been less than 12 hours.
9 o'clock!
Captain, what is it?
Potential target!
Keep your eyes peeled.
Did you see it right?
Adjusting recon route to 10 o'clock.
Something's here.
If hostiles are spotted,
cut off its retreat.
Chief, Sgt. Han has broken off.
Sgt. Han!
Sgt. Han? Sgt. Han?
Initiating search.
Lt. Shin take left, Sgt.
Park take right, now!
What the hell was it?
No visual, canvasing the premise, over.
Captain, do you copy?
Report continuously!
Yoo, follow me.
I'll debrief when everyone
reports back, over.
We were thorough, but we found nothing.
No sign of hostiles.
Chief, it was the North for sure.
We must tread carefully.
It's floating grass from the swamp.
We must investigate.
See? It was on.
As we expected, there was a detour.
But they're in pursuit of the target.
At current situation,
we can't disregard the fact
that all team may perish.
Yes, don't worry sir.
We're on a tight schedule,
you can't just jump into a swamp.
Master Sergeant…
Chief!
Bleeding occurred within the hour.
Sign of being dragged.
Move!
Follow me.
14 hours until the end of mission
Dragging stopped here.
Do not touch anything until further notice.
Yes, ma'am.
Chief!
It's Han's glove…
You're free to fire at hostiles.
3-2-2, 3-2-2.
Secure the swamp.
Body discovered.
Yoo, report in.
7 bodies confirmed.
Radio!
Nest, nest, this is eagle.
7 bodies found in S301 on SLL, over.
5 bodies are North Koreans
and 2 presumed allies.
Provoked by the North?
Where did the target attack from?
Secure the open area, and continue pursuit.
Copy that.
Over.
- This is Sgt. Lee!
- Don't touch!
One of the bodies is
Lee from the search party.
Resume pursuit, flank the swamp.
Chief!
Move!
Sir!
2 of those bodies are
from the search party.
Isn't finding them our primary objective?
Mission objective remains the same.
We evac after rescuing Han
and eliminating the target.
Potential biochemical target was sighted.
Rescuing Han is our priority, move!
Even if they find the deserted bunker,
we sealed it tight back in 2000.
Yes, don't worry, commander.
Why are you here, asshole!
How did you get in here!
I crawled in.
Since when? What did you hear?
What's all this?
Do you send in your men
knowing that they'll die?
- Tell me!
- Son of a bitch!
- Pull him out!
- Let go of me!
Let go!
Lt. Shin, can you hear me?!
Evac now! You'll die there!
MS2 bateriophage, you'll die, pull out now!
The colonel is…
Do you copy?
Chief!
I heard an order for evac, and a gunshot.
What? Radio in.
Nest, nest…
No signal.
Chief, the sample from the swamp
is showing positive reaction to nervine.
It's a confirmation of mutation.
Tell us what's really going on here.
Regardless of the mutation,
and the war room gunshot,
our primary objective
is to eliminate the target,
and evac with Sgt. Han.
Was I excluded
from any necessary intel?
What?
The target we're pursuing may not be human.
Something unimaginable…
That does not change our main objective.
No, which is why I'm bringing this up.
What the hell is going on?!
I didn't come here just to die,
tell us everything you know.
If you're scared, evac to the GP gate!
4 o'clock, source of the blast.
Move.
11 hours until the end of mission
Chief, a bunker sighted at 3 o'clock.
Radio!
2-1, 2-1.
Sir, comm signal is dropping.
Check team comm too.
2-1, 2-1.
There's radio interference
surrounding this area.
Get off comm.
Our target and Han are
likely inside the bunker
considering all circumstances.
We'll move in and eliminate.
Chief.
We must stay on our recon route, sir.
There's no actionable
intel that the target is inside.
Attention.
State your opinions.
If you wish to evac,
you have my permission.
I'll take the heat.
How can we leave Han behind!
Let's do it.
Like he said, let's get Han
and kill everything in there.
Park and I will take point,
deputy and Roh take the flank.
Rest of you cover the rear.
Chief.
Please put Roh on rear
and I'll take his place.
Yoo, are you okay?
Sure, no problem.
They're entering the bunker
that Ministry of Defense sealed.
There is a blood trail.
We have to investigate.
Drop your gun.
Now!
Order your team to come out.
Come on out!
Sons of traitors, one
slip and you'll go to hell.
Wanna see them die?!
Under attack!
Retrieve your weapon and confirm location!
Kill every last one of them!
Roh, provide cover!
Yoo!
Roh, get out of here!
Chief!
Master Sergeant! Cover fire!
Retreat.
Yoo! Cover the rear!
Sgt. Yoo…
Gu, get out of here...
Follow me.
2-1, 2-1?
Comm's down…
How the hell are you managing this?
My apologies, sir.
What's the post-op plan?
Biochemical specialist is part of the op,
I'll make sure this doesn't reach you.
Yes, sir.
5 hours until the end of mission
Colonel! All comms and
video feeds are down.
I'll go in myself.
Have a squad ready.
Yes, sir.
We have to find our men at once!
Sgt. Yoo?
What the…
What caused this?
Let's go back.
Look for survivors and secure a radio.
Chief…
Roh?
Sgt. Gu?
Where's the chief?
Weren't you with him?
The radio was hit during the firefight.
What?
What'll happen to us now?
Sgt. Yoo!
Yoo!
Stay awake, please!
Lieutenant.
It's…
too cold here.
Sergeant!
What about Gu?
Sergeant…
1 hour until the end of mission
Only an hour…
until evac.
When you encounter this unidentified being,
will you be able to
obtain DNA samples, and such,
will you step up and complete your duty?
Of course, sir.
It's a conspiracy from the top for sure.
I will not fall back like this.
There must have been
a bacterial experiment of some kind.
Considering physical symptoms
and involvement of the North,
carrier of this bio weapon
must be from the North.
We must
kill it before evac.
Could they've left us and
fallen back to the gate?
Only 19 days till my discharge.
I want to live…
Roh, listen to me.
Reach the recon route
and run for the GP gate.
By myself?
I'll look for the chief, so you go ahead.
Everyone here will die!
Get out of here!
11 o'clock, okay?
Just run!
Let's have a drink back at the base.
Come out!
Come at me, you fuck!
Get down!
Cover!
Have you forgotten our mission?!
Staff sergeant! Gu!
Don't move!
Lt. Shin, retreat to safety!
Hey, Choi Cheol.
Stop right there.
Do as you're told before
I put a bullet in you.
Why do you think I'm here?
What is your real mission?
Now you're curious?
Bastard.
Ask that in hell.
It's all over.
Go to hell!
What is the nature of that mutant?
Was it created in the North?
'Musudan', you mean?
When the mission
fails, you'll take the fall.
Stop!
Hey!
Deputy…
Lower your gun!
Shoot.
If you can't,
I'll kill him for you.
Why did the North create Musudan?
How could you let it to escape
even before we could put it in combat?!
Imagine what'd happen if
the agency found this out.
If you failed,
you and your team will
become Musudan! Got it?!
As an expert infiltrator,
comrade Li'll accompany you.
Complete your secondary
mission and kill him as you see fit.
How quickly does the
virus spread from the host?
It'll get increasingly
harder to contain it.
I came to kill it and bury it here.
It's what my friend wanted
before he turned into it.
We were fighting desperately to survive
when we met as orphans.
He was more important than family,
so it's my fate to send
him off to the afterlife.
If we can spread via body fluid
and blood with modifications,
we can wipe out South Korea.
Once the vaccine is
ready, put him in combat.
Right away!
Jae-hak…
It's the ultimate bio weapon
that'll annihilate USA and the South!
5 minutes over mission time
We've crossed S325.
Have the squad ready at the gate!
Sir, if Shin fails her mission,
I'll cover it up as a
provocation by the North.
Lieutenant.
If your mission is to kill that thing,
our goals are the same.
How about we team up?
Work side by side with the traitors?
Whether it heads south or north from here,
it'll wreak havoc either way.
Lieutenant.
Time's up.
If it came to,
can you promise that there'll
never be another Musudan?
Can you do that?
Hands up, fucker!
What's wrong?
This commie's holding a knife!
No, I was going to make a crutch…
Stand down.
I told Roh to keep close eye on Lt. Shin
before the mission began.
Due to optic nerves damage,
it is vulnerable to light.
Yes, colonel.
We'll enter on your order.
I'll end this. Yes, sir.
Is that...
your final bullet?
Look for proper C4 placement.
I'll go and be the lookout.
Roh.
Radio?
I can fix it, sir.
Head out and reestablish
contact no matter what it takes.
Sir?
If we fail,
you must inform the others
and eliminate Musudan.
Even if we succeed, you never saw it.
What do you mean?
That's how you live.
I understand.
I'll see you back at the base.
In one piece.
Okay.
No radio contact yet, sir.
As a backup I'm bringing
a biochemical specialist.
It's all or nothing.
We'll enter, sir.
Roll out!
We must lure it to the C4 and bury it.
If that fails, it's the end for us too.
I'll be the bait and lure it,
so bury me with my friend.
Take care of my fallen comrades too.
Head back alive.
Yo, Choi Cheol!
Toss the gun.
So this is how it ends.
2-1, 2-1!
Jae-hak…
come here.
Can you hear me?
Answer me!
It's me, Cheol.
Let's die together.
Lieutenant!
Chief!
Shoot!
2-1, 2-1!
Stop!
Where the hell are you?
I'm at S322, sir!
Secure the area at once.
Move!
What happened?
Where's Cpt. Jo?
Captain, Park, Yoo and Han are KIA…
Enough!
Retrieve the bodies first.
Only bodies of Cpt. Jo and
Gu haven't been recovered.
I've given you painkillers, and
stopped the bleeding, ma'am.
Good work, thanks.
Lieutenant, it's the colonel.
Great work.
Is the DNA sample secured?
I could not secure it, sir.
What? What do you mean?
5 of my men are dead or missing.
Haven't you heard?
You really did not secure it?
I could not, sir.
Recover Jo and Gu's bodies for now.
I searched thoroughly,
but it's not here, major.
I gave you an order before the mission!
Did you see her securing a sample?
What happened with the commies?
Il-kwon, Roh Il-kwon!
Look at me.
One word and you get
discharged with a reward.
And I get a promotion.
Il-kwon.
Or rot in military prison.
You conspired with the commies.
It's your call.
Honestly…
I didn't see whatever that was inside.
I only remember the
screams of the men who died.
Son of a bitch!
Salute!
Upon recovering the bodies,
the bunker is being resealed.
4 hours over mission time
Hold.
Lt. Shin, seal it properly and pull out!
For whom? My fallen comrades?
Do you want their deaths to be in vain?!
Move.
Move out.
This just in.
A military vehicle was
involved in an accident at 3PM.
Killing all passengers,
Ministry of Defense reported.
Cpt. Jo Jin-ho, Lt. Lee Hyun-suk,
Master Sgt. Park Sang-chul…
It'll get increasingly
harder to contain it.
I will…
kill it for good.